Guide to the Edward Flanders Ricketts Papers, 1936-1979 (inclusive), 1936-1947 (bulk)
Department of Special Collections
Edward Flanders Ricketts Papers,
1936-1979 (inclusive), 1936-1947 (bulk)
Special Collections M0291
Ricketts, Edward Flanders, 1896-1948.
7.5 linear ft.
Stanford University. Libraries. Dept. of Special Collections and University Archives.
Personal and professional papers including incoming and outgoing correspondence, a few letters from Herbert Kline to John Steinbeck, notes on intertidal marine life, printed articles, manuscript notes of unpublished biology articles, a philosophical manuscript, financial records, photographs and notes from trips to West Vancouver Island and the Queen Charlotte Islands prepared by Ricketts for the use of John Steinbeck. Also includes notes and other materials used for additions and revisions of Ricketts' publication, Between Pacific Tides, and correspondence about the book.
Administrative Information
Access
The Elizabeth Ott correspondence is restricted.
Acquisition Information
Transfer from Hopkins Marine Station, 1974, and Peter Lisca, 1991.
Biography
Edward Flanders Robb Ricketts was born in Chicago, Illinois May 14, 1897. From 1923 until his death in 1948, Ricketts lived in the Monterey, California area where he pursued his career as a marine biologist and became good friends with John Steinbeck.
Scope and Content
Personal and professional papers including incoming and outgoing correspondence, a few letters from Herbert Kline to John Steinbeck, notes on intertidal marine life, printed articles, manuscript notes of unpublished biology articles, a philosophical manuscript, financial records, photographs and notes from trips to West Vancouver Island and the Queen Charlotte Islands prepared by Ricketts for the use of John Steinbeck. Also includes notes and other materials used for additions and revisions of Ricketts' publication, Between Pacific Tides, and correspondence about the book.
Indexing Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the library's online public access catalog.
Belloc, Hilary.; Belloc, Hope; Berkeley, Cyril; Cage, Xenia; Campbell, Joseph, 1904-; Deichmann, Elisabeth; Faure, Raoul C.; Field, Sara Bard, 1882-1974; Hedgepeth, Joel W.; Kline, Herbert; Miller, Henry, 1891-; Scardigli, Virginia; Steinbeck, John, 1902-1968; Street, Webster; Wood, Charles Erskine Scott, 1852-1944; American Museum of Natural History; Pacific Biological Laboratories; Oceanography--Pacific Ocean; Marine biology--Research; Marine ecology; Charts; Graphs; Notebooks; Photoprints; Surveys
Collection Contents
- Professional Work, Series 1
  - Pacific Biological Laboratories -- Client and source files for biological materials, Subseries 1.1
    - Alabama, 1945 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence, invoices
    - Arizona, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, invoices
    - Arkansas, 1936-1939 (Box 1, Folder 3)
      - Correspondence, invoices
    - California
      - Berkeley
        - Cutter Laboratories, 1937 (Box 1, Folder 4)
          - Correspondence, invoices
        - University Apparatus, 1945-1948 (Box 1, Folder 5)
          - Correspondence, invoices, packing sheets
        - University Apparatus, 1942-1944 (Box 1, Folder 6)
          - Correspondence, invoices, packing sheets
        - University Apparatus, 1937-1941 (Box 1, Folder 7)
          - Correspondence, invoices, packing sheets
        - University of California, 1940 (Box 1, Folder 8)
          - Invoices
      - Davis
        - National Insect Co., 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 8)
          - Correspondence, invoices
      - Eureka
        - Central Fish and Oyster Co., 1944 (Box 1, Folder 8)
          - Correspondence, invoices
      - Glendale
        - California Insectaries/California Biological Supply, 1939-1942 (Box 1, Folder 9)
          - Correspondence, invoices
      - Hollywood
        - Disney Studios, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 9)
          - Order for amoeba
      - Los Angeles
        - Braun Corp., 1937-1941 (Box 1, Folder 10)
          - Purchase orders
        - Central Scientific Co., n.d. (Box 1, Folder 11)
          - Order
        - J.M. Dannaldson, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 11)
          - Catalog request
        - Western Scientific Co., 1937-1938 (Box 1, Folder 11)
          - Orders
      - Menlo Park
        - Harold Hoss, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 12)
          - Order & EFR's notes
      - Monterey
        - American Fish Co., 1937-1945 (Box 1, Folder 12)
          - Invoices
        - Central California Fish Co., 1937 (Box 1, Folder 12)
          - Invoices
        - California Packing Co., 1938 (Box 1, Folder 12)
          - Correspondence
        - Monterey Union High School, 1947 (Box 1, Folder 12)
          - Invoice
      - San Francisco
        - Braun-Knecht-Heimann Co., 1937-1942 (Box 1, Folder 13)
          - Price lists, purchase orders, shipping receipts, correspondence
        - Braun-Knecht-Heimann Co., 1943-1945 (Box 1, Folder 14)
          - Price lists, purchase orders, shipping receipts, correspondence
        - Braun-Knecht-Heimann Co., 1946-1947 (Box 1, Folder 15)
          - Price lists, purchase orders, shipping receipts, correspondence
        - California Poultry Co., 1937-1944 (Box 2, Folder 1)
          - Invoices, correspondence
        - S.C. Marcuse Co., 1937-1944 (Box 2, Folder 1)
          - Invoices, correspondence
        - A. Paladini, Inc., 1937-1944 (Box 2, Folder 2)
          - Invoices, correspondence
        - Pennington Pet Co., 1937 (Box 2, Folder 2)
          - Correspondence
        - Redmond Scientific Co., 1938 (Box 2, Folder 2)
          - Correspondence
        - Ansel W. Robinson, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 2)
          - Correspondence
        - Sullivan's Pet Shop, Inc., 1937 (Box 2, Folder 2)
          - Correspondence
        - Swift and Co., 1938-1945 (Box 2, Folder 2)
          - Correspondence, orders
      - San Rafael
        - Marin Municipal Waterworks, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 3)
          - Correspondence
    - Colorado
      - Boulder
        - University of Colorado, 1938-1943 (Box 2, Folder 4)
          - Correspondence, invoices, orders, bills of lading
    - Connecticut
      - New Haven
        - Yale University, 1940-1943 (Box 2, Folder 4)
          - Correspondence, orders
    - District of Columbia
      - The Army War College, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 4)
        - Correspondence
    - Florida
      - Englewood
        - Zoological Research Supply, 1937-1940 (Box 2, Folder 5)
          - Correspondence, price lists
      - Ocala
        - Tyler and Needham, 1938-1939 (Box 2, Folder 5)
          - Correspondence
      - Silver Springs
        - Ross Allen's Reptile Institute, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 5)
          - Brochures & price list
      - Tallahassee
        - University of Florida, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 5)
          - Brochures & price list
    - Georgia
      - Atlanta
        - Emory University, 1938 (Box 2, Folder 6)
          - Correspondence, price list
    - Hawaii
      - Honolulu
        - University of Hawaii, 1937-1947 (Box 2, Folder 6)
          - Correspondence, orders
    - Illinois
      - Chicago
        - Beckley Cardy Co., 1937-1943 (Box 2, Folder 7)
          - Correspondence, orders
        - Cardevant Labs, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 7)
          - Correspondence, EFR notes
        - Chicago Apparatus Co., 1937-1943 (Box 2, Folder 8)
          - Correspondence, orders, invoices, price lists, EFR notes
        - Chicago Natural History Museum (formerly Field Museum of Natural History), 1946 (Box 2, Folder 9)
          - Correspondence, orders
        - Coe-Palm Biological Supply House, 1946-1947 (Box 2, Folder 9)
          - Correspondence, orders
        - Denoyer Geppert Co., 1937-1946 (Box 2, Folder 9)
          - Correspondence, orders, price quotes
        - General Biological Supply House, 1939-1947 (Box 2, Folder 10)
          - Correspondence, invoices, EFR notes, orders
        - Illinois Biological Supply Co./National Biological Supply Co., 1937-1947 (Box 2, Folder 11)
          - Correspondence, orders
        - Northwestern University, 1937-1943 (Box 2, Folder 11)
          - Correspondence
        - Saikin Biological Laboratories, 1937-1943 (Box 2, Folder 11)
          - Correspondence, supply lists
        - Scientific Apparatus Makers of America, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 11)
          - Correspondence
        - W.W. Welch Manufacturing Co., 1937-1947 (Box 2, Folder 12)
          - Correspondence, orders, price lists, EFR notes
      - Elsah
        - The Principia College of Liberal Arts, 1940 (Box 2, Folder 12)
          - Correspondence
      - Lisle
        - St. Precopius College, 1938-1945 (Box 2, Folder 12)
          - Correspondence, EFR notes, prices, orders
      - Urbana
        - University of Illinois, 1942-1943 (Box 2, Folder 12)
          - Correspondence, orders
    - Indiana
      - Bloomington
        - Indiana University, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 13)
          - Correspondence
      - Delphi
        - Villa Alba Laboratory, 1937-1940 (Box 2, Folder 13)
          - Correspondence, invoices
      - North Judson
        - A.A. Sphung and J.L. Currier, 1939 (Box 2, Folder 13)
          - Correspondence
    - Iowa
      - Ames
        - Iowa State College, 1937-1943 (Box 2, Folder 14)
          - Correspondence, price lists
      - Dubuque
        - University of Dubuque, 1937 (Box 2, Folder 14)
          - Correspondence
      - Iowa City
        - Iowa State University, 1939-1943 (Box 2, Folder 14)
          - Correspondence, orders
    - Kansas
      - Lawrence
        - University of Kansas, 1938-1943 (Box 2, Folder 15)
          - Correspondence, orders
      - Topeka/Winfield
        - Quivira Specialties Co./Charles E. Burt, 1939-1946 (Box 2, Folder 16)
          - Invoices
        - Quivira Specialties Co./Charles E. Burt, 1937-1939 (Box 2, Folder 17)
          - Correspondence, price lists, EFR notes
        - Quivira Specialties Co./Charles E. Burt, 1940-1942 (Box 3, Folder 1)
          - Correspondence, orders, price lists, EFR notes
        - Quivira Specialties Co./Charles E. Burt, 1942-1947 (Box 3, Folder 2)
          - Correspondence, orders, price lists
    - Louisiana
      - New Orleans
        - Southern Biological Supply Co., 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 3)
          - Correspondence, invoices, book review of Pondfish Culture by Percy Viosca
        - Tulane University, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 3)
          - Correspondence
      - Thibodeaux
        - Tom Haydel, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 3)
          - Shipping label, EFR notes
    - Maryland
      - Baltimore
        - Johns Hopkins University, 1937-1943 (Box 3, Folder 4)
          - Correspondence, price lists
    - Massachusetts
      - Boston
        - Camboso Scientific Co., 1939-1943 (Box 3, Folder 5)
          - Correspondence, orders
      - Cambridge
        - Harvard University, 1943-1944 (Box 3, Folder 5)
          - Correspondence
        - Museum of Comparative Zoology (Harvard University), 1940-1945 (Box 3, Folder 5)
          - Correspondence
      - Northampton
        - Smith College, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 5)
          - Correspondence
      - Wellesley
        - Wellesley College, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 5)
          - Correspondence
      - Wood's Hole
        - Marine Biological Laboratory, 1937-1946 (Box 3, Folder 6)
          - Correspondence, receipts, orders, EFR notes
      - Worcester
        - Holy Cross College, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 6)
          - Order
    - Michigan
      - Ann Arbor
        - M.E. Van Ells, 1937-1947 (Box 3, Folder 7)
          - Correspondence, receipts, price lists, EFR notes
        - M.E. Van Ells, 1939-1946 (Box 3, Folder 8)
          - Invoices
      - Detroit
        - Cass Technical High School, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 9)
          - Correspondence
      - Dexter
        - Michigan Biological Supply Co., Inc., 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 9)
          - Correspondence, receipts, invoices, EFR notes
    - Minnesota
      - Minneapolis
        - Trans-Mississippi Biological Supply, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 10)
          - Correspondence
        - University of Minnesota, 1938-1943 (Box 3, Folder 10)
          - Correspondence, orders, receipts, price lists
      - Rochester
        - Mayo Clinic, 1937 (Box 3, Folder 10)
          - Correspondence
      - St. Paul
        - Macalester College, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 10)
          - Correspondence, order
    - Missouri
      - Columbia
        - University of Missouri, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 11)
          - Correspondence
    - New Mexico
      - Portales
        - David R. Gwin, 1937-1940 (Box 3, Folder 11)
          - Correspondence, price lists, EFR notes
    - Nebraska
      - Lincoln
        - Powers and Powers, 1937-1942 (Box 3, Folder 12)
          - Correspondence
        - University of Nebraska, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 12)
          - Correspondence
        - Western Biological Laboratories, 1941 (Box 3, Folder 12)
          - Correspondence
    - Nevada
      - Reno
        - University of Nevada, 1937-1942 (Box 3, Folder 12)
          - Correspondence, order, price lists
    - New Jersey
      - New Brunswick
        - Rutgers University, 1936-1943 (Box 3, Folder 13)
          - Correspondence, orders, price lists
      - Princeton
        - Princeton University, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 13)
          - Correspondence
    - New York
      - Brooklyn
        - James R. Bartholomew (fr. Harvard University), 1938-1939 (Box 3, Folder 14)
          - Correspondence
        - Brooklyn College, 1941-1942 (Box 3, Folder 14)
          - Correspondence, orders, price lists
        - Park Biological Supply, 1937-1940 (Box 3, Folder 14)
          - Correspondence, invoices
        - Charles O. Schoof, 1939 (Box 3, Folder 14)
          - Correspondence
      - Ithaca
        - Cornell University, 1938-1943 (Box 3, Folder 14)
          - Correspondence, orders
      - New York City
        - Columbia University, 1939-1943 (Box 3, Folder 14)
          - Correspondence, orders, invoices
        - Hunter College, 1940 (Box 3, Folder 14)
          - Correspondence, orders
        - New York Scientific Company, 1937-1947 (Box 3, Folder 15)
          - Correspondence, orders, price lists
        - Standard Scientific Supply Corporation, 1937-1939 (Box 3, Folder 15)
          - Correspondence, orders, price lists
      - Rochester
        - Biological Supply Corporation, 1937-1945 (Box 3, Folder 16)
          - Correspondence, orders
        - Wards Natural Science Establishment, Inc., 1936-1946 (Box 3, Folder 17)
          - Correspondence, orders, receipts, price lists
        - Walter F. Webb, 1941-1942 (Box 3, Folder 17)
          - Correspondence, price list
    - North Carolina
      - Elon College
        - Carolina Biological Supply Company, 1937-1946 (Box 3, Folder 18)
          - Correspondence, orders, price list
    - Ohio
      - Cleveland
        - Western Reserve University, 1943 (Box 3, Folder 19)
          - Correspondence, order
      - Columbus
        - University of Ohio, 1938-1943 (Box 3, Folder 19)
          - Correspondence
      - Salem
        - John P. Sharp, M.D., 1941 (Box 3, Folder 19)
          - Correspondence
      - West Elkton
        - The Highland Apiaries, 1938 (Box 3, Folder 19)
          - Price lists
    - Oklahoma
      - Muskegee
        - Max Hamilton, 1941-1942 (Box 4, Folder 1)
          - Correspondence
      - Norman
        - University of Oklahoma, 1937-1946 (Box 4, Folder 1)
          - Correspondence, orders, price lists, bills
      - Oklahoma City
        - Board of Public Affairs, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 1)
          - EFR notes
      - Weatherford
        - Southwestern State College, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 1)
          - Correspondence, orders
    - Oregon
      - Portland
        - Chamber of Commerce, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 2)
          - Correspondence
        - Jake's Famous Crawfish, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 2)
          - Correspondence
        - Oregon Biological Supply Co., 1936-1937 (Box 4, Folder 3)
          - Correspondence, invoices, orders, EFR notes
        - Oregon Biological Supply Co., 1937-1945 (Box 4, Folder 4)
          - Correspondence, invoices, orders, EFR notes
        - Oregon Biological Supply Co., 1940; n.d. (Box 4, Folder 5)
          - Invoices
        - Tint's Fishmarket, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 6)
          - Correspondence
    - Pennsylvania
      - Meadville
        - Paul E. Webb, 1937-1943 (Box 4, Folder 7)
          - Correspondence
      - Pittsburgh
        - Pennsylvania Farmer, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 7)
          - Correspondence
        - University of Pittsburgh, 1938-1943 (Box 4, Folder 7)
          - Correspondence
      - State College
        - Pennsylvania State College, 1943 (Box 4, Folder 7)
          - Correspondence
    - Puerto Rico
      - San Juan
        - Jose Oliver Gonzalez, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 8)
          - Correspondence
        - University of Puerto Rico, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 8)
          - Correspondence
    - Rhode Island
      - Kingston
        - Rhode Island State College, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 8)
          - Correspondence, invoices, orders
    - South Carolina
      - Aiken
        - Hendersons & Salley, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 9)
          - Correspondence re: Chicora College
    - Tennessee
      - Memphis
        - Technical Products Co., 1937 (Box 4, Folder 9)
          - Correspondence, price lists
    - Texas
      - Fort Worth
        - Christian University, 1938-1942 (Box 4, Folder 9)
          - Correspondence
      - Houston
        - Rice Institute, 1939-1942 (Box 4, Folder 9)
          - Correspondence, orders
    - Utah
      - Mt. Pleasant
        - Wasatch Academy, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 10)
          - Correspondence
      - Salt Lake City
        - University of Utah, 1937-1940 (Box 4, Folder 10)
          - Correspondence, orders, invoices, price lists
    - Virginia
      - Lynchburg
        - Randolph-Macon Woman's College, 1938-1940 (Box 4, Folder 10)
          - Correspondence, orders
      - Petersburg
        - Virginia State College, 1942 (Box 4, Folder 10)
          - Correspondence
    - Wisconsin
      - Madison
        - University of Wisconsin, 1942-1946 (Box 4, Folder 11)
          - Correspondence, orders, invoices
      - Oshkosh
        - Lemberger's, 1945-1946 (Box 4, Folder 11)
          - Correspondence, orders, supply list
        - E.G. Steinhilber, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 11)
          - Correspondence
    - Australia
      - Melbourne
        - University of Melbourne, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 12)
          - Correspondence
    - Canada
      - Alberta
        - Edmonton
          - University of Alberta, 1937-1940 (Box 4, Folder 12)
            - Correspondence, orders
      - British Columbia
        - Shawnigan Lake
          - Shawnigan Lake School, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 12)
            - Correspondence, orders
        - Victoria
          - Victoria College, 1937-1946 (Box 4, Folder 12)
            - Correspondence, orders, invoices
      - Manitoba
        - Winnipeg
          - University of Manitoba, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 12)
            - Correspondence
      - Ontario
        - Toronto
          - University of Toronto, 1941 (Box 4, Folder 12)
            - Correspondence
      - Quebec
        - Montreal
          - McGill University, 1945-1947 (Box 4, Folder 12)
            - Correspondence
    - China
      - Soochow
        - Soochow University, 1936-1937 (Box 4, Folder 13)
          - Correspondence, Biological Support Service bulletins
    - Great Britain
      - England
        - Bath
          - Dr. F.H. Edgeworth, 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 13)
            - Correspondence
        - Bridlington
          - Gautier's Baths, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 13)
            - Correspondence, receipts
        - Buckingham
          - Stowe School, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 13)
            - Correspondence
        - London
          - Birkbeck College (University of London), 1937 (Box 4, Folder 13)
            - Correspondence
        - Manchester
          - Flatters & Garnett, Ltd., 1937 (Box 4, Folder 13)
            - Correspondence
          - H. Gunnery, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 13)
            - Correspondence
      - Scotland
        - Glasgow
          - University of Glasgow, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 13)
            - Correspondence
    - India
      - Lucknow
        - The University, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 14)
          - Correspondence
    - Japan
      - Tokyo
        - Shibayama Natural Science Laboratory, Inc., 1937; n.d. (Box 4, Folder 14)
          - Correspondence, price lists, circulars
    - Philippines
      - Manila
        - Ateneo de Manila, 1938-1941 (Box 4, Folder 14)
          - Correspondence
        - Deogracias Villadolid, 1938-1939 (Box 4, Folder 14)
          - Correspondence
  - Pacific Biological Laboratories -- Collectors, Subseries 1.2
    - Price lists to collectors, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 15)
    - Major Berry, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 16)
      - EFR notes
    - "Gabe" Harold Bicknell, 1937-1940 (Box 4, Folder 17)
      - Correspondence, some with Stnaley Erickson
    - Blankenship, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 18)
      - EFR notes
    - C. Bushnell, 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 18)
      - EFR notes
    - A.O. Chandler, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 18)
      - Correspondence, EFR notes
    - Abe Cook, 1939-1940 (Box 4, Folder 18)
      - Correspondence, EFR notes
    - Harold Dahl, 1944 (Box 4, Folder 19)
      - Correspondence
    - Death Valley Curley [Roscoe C. Wright], 1937 (Box 4, Folder 19)
      - Correspondence
    - Stanley Erickson, 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 19)
      - Correspondence, EFR notes (see also "Gabe" Bicknell)
    - Norm [Geschwind], 1943 (Box 4, Folder 19)
      - List of species collected
    - James Grantham, n.d.
    - Harlan B. Hess, 1937-1938 (Box 4, Folder 19)
      - Correspondence
    - Murray B. Hood, 1940 (Box 4, Folder 19)
      - Correspondence
    - King, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 19)
      - EFR notes
    - Ralph / Roy Lehman, 1937-1940; n.d. (Box 4, Folder 20)
      - Correspondence, EFR notes (some joint with Cleo Oxford, Ralph Polston, and A.J. Swan)
    - Ray Meredith, 1938 (Box 4, Folder 21)
      - Correspondence, EFR notes (some joint with James Grantham)
    - Cleo Oxford, 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 21)
      - Correspondence, EFR notes (some joint with Roy Lehman)
    - Ralph Pulston, n.d.
    - Nan Ricketts, 1938-1940 (Box 4, Folder 21)
      - Statements, invoices
    - A.J. Swan, 1946
    - Blackie Thompson, 1939 (Box 4, Folder 22)
      - EFR notes
    - Mr. & Mrs. Ben Wehe, 1937-1939 (Box 4, Folder 22)
      - Correspondence
    - J. Widmaier, n.d. (Box 4, Folder 22)
      - EFR notes
    - Roscoe C. Wright
    - Yuen Yin, 1937 (Box 4, Folder 22)
      - EFR notes, list of specimens received
  - Pacific Biological Laboratories -- Equipment suppliers, Subseries 1.3
    - Acme Business Equipment Co., 1937 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Invoice
    - Boyle Manufacturing Co., Inc., 1937 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence, invoice
    - Braun-Knecht-Heimann Co., 1939-1940 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Invoices
    - Cemetex Co., 1940 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence, latex sample stuck to folder
    - Central Scientific Co., 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence
    - Commercial Solvents Co., 1937 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Invoice, denatured alcohol formulas
    - Cooke's Advertising and Printing, 1946 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Invoices
    - H.S. Crocker Co., Inc., 1937 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence
    - Fisher Scientific Co. (Pittsburgh), 1936-1945 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Invoices, EFR notes, pump specifications
    - Fisher Scientific Co. (St. Louis), 1946 (Box 5, Folder 1)
      - Correspondence, ad
    - Charles R. Hadley Co., 1937-1938 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, invoices
    - Hazel-Atlas Glass Co., 1942 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence
    - Joy's, 1937-1939 (Box 5, Folder 2)
      - Correspondence, invoices
    - Kimble Glass Co., 1937 (Box 5, Folder 2)